<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tabou</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_settings">About</string>
    <string name="about_description">Tabou is an educational game meant for players to practice French vocabulary with a game similar to charades.\n\nSETUP\nThe game is played with 4-12 players, and there are two teams. All players sit in a circle so that the teams are alternating. For example, a player on team 1 has a team 2 player on his right and a team 2 player on his left. Similarly, a player on team 2 has a team 1 player on his right and on his left.\n\nBASIC INSTRUCTIONS\nA player on team 1 begins with the app and is known as the describer. On the first screen, there is the target word in bold. The describer\'s goal is to describe this word to his team, so that someone else on his team shouts out that exact word. The catch is the describer cannot use any of the tabou words listed below the target word. If he accidentally uses one of the target words, he has to click pass to get a new word, and his team gets no points. An adjacent player on team 2 can view the device to make sure no tabou words are used. For each target word guessed correctly by the describer\'s team, one point is earned. If the describer does not know the meaning of the target word, he may press the translate button and lose one point for his team. Alternatively, he can click pass and receive a new card with no penalty. The describer goes through as many target words as possible until the 60 second timer runs out. Once time is up, the describer passes the device to the right, so the person to his right is now the describer. At this point, team 2 tries to guess the target word to earn team 2 points.\n\nNOT ALLOWED\nThe describer cannot use gestures, sounds or drawings when describing the target word. The describer can sing, but cannot hum or whistle a tune without words.\n\nENDING THE GAME\nOnce all players have taken a turn as the describer, the game is over, and the winning team is the team with the most points.\n\nLEVELS\nThe easy level only has 3 tabou words, the medium level has 4 tabou words and the hard level has 5 tabou words.
</string>
</resources>
